A Finding Aid to the Werner Drewes Papers, 1838-2015, bulk 1890-1990, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Werner Drewes papers
1838-2015
bulk 1890-1990
Archives of American Art
Drewes, Werner, 1899-1985
AAA.drewwern
Archival Resource Key
15.76 Linear feet
The papers of painter, printmaker, designer, and teacher, Werner Drewes, measure 15.76 linear feet and date from 1838-2015, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1890s-1990s. The papers document Drewes' life and career through biographical and family material; correspondence with family members, artists, galleries, and art institutions and organizations; scattered teaching notes and writings including a diary; catalogs and inventories of artwork; three scrapbooks; printed material; 38 sketchbooks, loose sketches, and prints; and photographs of Drewes, his family, friends and colleagues, exhibitions, travels, and works of art. Also found are scattered papers of Drewes' second wife, Maria Drewes.
Scope and Contents
The papers of painter, printmaker, designer, and teacher, Werner Drewes, measure 15.76 linear feet and date from 1838-2015, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1890s-1990s. The papers document Drewes' life and career through biographical and family material; correspondence with family members, artists, galleries, and art institutions and organizations; scattered teaching notes and writings including a diary; catalogs and inventories of artwork; three scrapbooks; printed material; 38 sketchbooks, loose sketches, and prints; and photographs of Drewes, his family, friends and colleagues, exhibitions, travels, and works of art. Also found are scattered papers of Drewes' second wife, Maria Drewes.
Biographical material documents Drewes' family history through family trees and biographical notes made by family members, and also includes 3 of Drewes' passports, some student and military records, resumés, and a partial interview transcript.
Correspondence is with family members; artists including Ed Boccia, Thomas Eldred, T. Lux Feininger, Clark Fitzgerald, Wassily Kandinsky, Jean Helion, Gerhard Marcks, Arthur Osver, Karl Schrag, and Albert Urban; and galleries and art organizations and institutions such as Richard York Gallery, the Smithsonian Institution, and others. Correspondence also relates to the Drewes estate, as well as to loans, exhibitions and sales of artwork.
Notes and writings include a diary kept by Drewes between 1918-1920 in Europe, a "love letter" in verse form written by Drewes to his first wife, Margaret, some teaching notes and notes on design, and 2 essays about Drewes written by others.
Catalogs and inventory records provide comprehensive documentation of the artwork Drewes created over the course of his career. Entries include titles, assigned numbers, subjects, dimensions, media used, and sketches or photos of artwork.
Three scrapbooks provide scattered documentation of Drewes' life and career, and include clippings from the 1920s and 1930s, and a scrapbook created by Maria Drewes for her husband's memorial service.
Printed material includes event announcements and exhibition catalogs, as well as news clippings tracing Drewes' career from the 1920s to the 1980s.
Artwork consists of greeting cards made by Drewes, as well as 38 sketchbooks and numerous loose sketches in pencil, ink, watercolor, and crayon.
Photographic material includes vintage family photographs, prints, negatives, slide tranparencies, and 8 glass plate negatives, of Drewes, his family and friends, events including exhibitions and travels, and artwork.
Found in Maria Drewes' papers are correspondence, 17 diaries primarily documenting travels with Werner Drewes, two scrapbooks with designs for jewelry, and photos of family, friends and jewelry.
Biographical / Historical
Painter, printmaker and designer Werner Drewes (1899-1985) was born in Canig, Germany, and immigrated to the United States in 1930. A student of the Bauhaus, and a prolific artist and teacher, Drewes worked with many kinds of media and produced numerous woodcuts, etchings, oils, watercolors, drawings and collages over the course of his life.
Drewes served for two years on Germany's Western Front during World War 1, before studying at the Bauhaus, Weimar, from 1921-1922. He then traveled throughout Europe, Asia and North and South America with his wife Margaret before returning to Germany in 1927 and enrolling at the Bauhaus, Dessau. During his time there Drewes forged his artistic ideas from the radical influences of renowned architects and artists including Lyonel Feininger, Johannes Itten, Wassily Kandinsky, Paul Klee, and Oscar Schlemmer, and learned the Bauhaus teaching approach that would serve him throughout his career. In 1930 Drewes, Margaret, and their 2 young sons emigrated to the United States and settled in New York City where Drewes attended the Art Students League. From 1935-1936 he taught drawing and printmaking at the Brooklyn Museum School as an employee of the Works Progress Administration Federal Art Project (WPA FAP). In 1936 he became a founding member of American Abstract Artists and the following year joined the American Artists' Congress and became an American citizen. From 1937-1940 he taught painting and printmaking at Columbia University.
In the early 1940s Drewes taught at the Master Institute in Riverside Museum, New York City, and worked as a technical supervisor for the Graphic Art Division of the FAP. From 1944-1945 he worked at Stanley William Hayter's Atelier 17 improving his intaglio technique and then teaching design, printmaking and photography at Brooklyn College. In 1946 he taught design at the Institute of Design in Chicago before being appointed Professor of Design at the School of Fine Arts of Washington University in Saint Louis, where he continued to teach until his retirement in 1965.
Following Margaret's death in 1959, Drewes married jewelry designer and fellow professor of Washington University, Mary (Maria) Louise Lischer in 1960. On Drewes' retirement he and Maria moved to Pennsylvania where he continued to paint, focusing primarily on still lifes and landscapes. He moved to Washington in 1972 and published his American Indians portfolio, before finally setting in Reston, Virginia, where the Rose Catalog of his prints was published and where he lived as a working and exhibiting artist until his death in 1985.
In October 1984 a comprehensive retrospective, Sixty-Five Years of Printmaking, was held at the then named Smithsonian's National Museum of American Art. Drewes' work can be found in the collections of the Brooklyn Museum, the Metropolitan Museum of Art, Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, Museum of Modern Art, National Gallery of Art, New York Public Library, Smithsonian American Art Museum, and the Whitney Museum of American Art.
Arrangement
Missing Title
Series 1: Biographical Material, 1838-1980s (0.4 linear feet; Boxes 1, 16)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1878-2004 (1.2 linear feet; Boxes 1-2, 16)
Series 3: Notes and Writings, 1922-2002 (0.5 linear feet; Box 2)
Series 4: Catalogs and Inventory Records, circa 1919-circa 1980s (2.3 linear feet; Boxes 2-6)
Series 5: Scrapbooks, 1920s-1985 (3 folders; Box 5)
Series 6: Printed Material, 1897-2015 (1 linear feet; Boxes 5-6)
Series 7: Artwork and Sketchbooks, circa 1890s-2002 (3.67 linear feet; Boxes 6-9, 16-17)
Series 8: Photographic Material, circa 1890s-2000 (5.53 linear feet; Boxes 9-14, 17, MGP 2)
Series 9: Mary (Maria) Louise Lischer Drewes Papers, 1930s-1980s (1 linear foot; Box 15)
Many of the records were assigned color-coded alpha-numeric labels prior to donation. In series where these labeling systems predominate, material has been arranged according to those systems and all previously assigned labels are indicated in the Container Listing. Many folder titles are taken from the original labels. Glass plate negatives are housed separately and closed to researchers.
The collection is arranged as 9 series.
Conditions Governing Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Washington, D.C. Research Center. Glass plate negatives are housed separately and not served to researchers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Werner Drewes papers were donated in 2005 by Werner Drewes' sons Wolfram U. Drewes, Harald D. Drewes, and Bernard W. Drewes. 4 additional items were donated by Karen Seibert, Drewes granddaughter, in 2015. Some material had been previously loaned for microfilming in 1979, and was subsequently included in the 2005 gift.
Existence and Location of Copies
Portions of the collection are availalbe on 35mm microfilm reels 1497-1498 at the Archives of American Art offices and through interlibrary loan. Researchers should note that the arrangement of the material described in the container inventory does not reflect the arrangement of the collection on microfilm.
Educators -- Virginia; Transcripts; Painters -- Virginia -- Reston; Art -- Study and teaching; Designers -- Virginia; Prints; Photographs; Sketchbooks; Scrapbooks; Diaries; Printmakers -- Virginia -- Reston; Interviews; Greeting cards; Smithsonian Institution; Boccia, Edward, 1921-2012; Drewes, Maria; Eldred, Thomas; Feininger, T. Lux; Fitz-Gerald, Clark B. (Clark Battle), 1917-2004; Hélion, Jean, 1904-1987; Kandinsky, Wassily, 1866-1944; Marcks, Gerhard; Osver, Arthur, 1912-2006; Schrag, Karl; Urban, Albert; Richard York Gallery
- Biographical Material, 1838-1980s; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 0.4 Linear feet Boxes 1, 16
  Arrangement
  Some of the material in this series was labeled with green and yellow stickers as the "G" and "Y" series. Material is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  Scope and Contents
  Included here are Drewes' 1923, 1926 and 1932 passports, his student record from the Bahaus School of Design signed by Mies van der Rohe and Wassily Kandinsky, some military papers, resumes and biographical notes, and an incomplete transcript of an interview with Drewes.
  Also found is information relating to Drewes' family history, including family trees, a coat of arms, family letters and notebooks, and a book of handwritten poetry belonging to Drewes' mother. Much of this material is in German.
  - Address Book (G28), circa 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Awards and Certificates, circa 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bauhaus Student Record, Passports and Military Documents, 1899-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Calendar, 1921; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Family History, 1838-1930s; 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
    OV material housed in Box 16, Folder 1
  - Family History (G2, G6), circa 1920s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Family History Notes (G11), 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Interview Transcript (incomplete) of Interview of Drewes by Martina Roudabush Norelli for the Smithsonian National Museum of American Art (Y42), 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1917, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Poetry Book of Martha Schaefer (Drewes) (G10), 1880s-1890s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Resumés (Y39), circa 1960s-circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Resumés and Biographical Notes, circa 1950s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Who's Who Entries, circa 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Oversized Family History from Box 1, Folder 5, Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1878-2004; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 1.2 Linear feet Boxes 1-2, 16
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  Found in this series are letters from Maria Drewes and other family members, and artists and art dealers including Josef Albers, Edward Boccia, Alexander Calder, Howard Dearstyne, Bourgoyne Diller, Katherine S. Dreier, Perle Fine, Adolph Gottlieb, Herbert Grainick, Jean Helion, Carl Holty, Wassily Kandinsky, Gerhard Marcks, Laszlo Moholy-Nagy, Hans Moller, Abraham Rattner, Richard York Gallery, Kurt Roesch, Karl Schrag, Albert Urban, and others. Some individual correspondents have named files, while others are included in the "General" files.
  General correspondence and general business correspondence include correspondence with art galleries, and art institutions, including the Smithsonian Institution, and relate primarily to loans, sales, and exhibitions of artwork.
  Correspondence relating to the Drewes' estate includes an appraisal report by Karen Holtzman for Drewes' artwork and correspondence between family members, including Harald and Wolfram Drewes, and inventories of artwork.
  One folder relates to a 1974 exhibition in Turkey and Greece, and includes photographs and publicity material from the exhibition. A folder of correspondence labeled with a "Y" series of yellow stickers includes letters from T. Lux Feininger, Clark Fitzgerald, Karl Schrag, and Swedish artists Jan and Pia Thunholm.
  Greeting cards consist of hand made cards sent to Drewes by artists including Gerhard Marcks, Karl Schrag and others.
  - Berlin Visit, 1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Boccia, Ed, 1969-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Condolence Letters on Death of Margaret Drewes, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Drewes Estate, 1987-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Drewes Estate, Holtzmann Appraisal Report, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18-20)
  - Drewes, Mary (Maria) Louise, from Werner Drewes (Y5), circa 1960-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Drewes, Mary (Maria) Louise, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Eldred, Edna and Thomas (Y43), circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Exhibition, Werner Drewes-Baski Sanati (1974), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Family Letters (G14, G15), 1878-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - General, A-B, circa 1930s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - General C, 1966-1980s; 1934; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - General, D-F, circa 1930s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - General, G-I, circa 1940s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - General, J-L, 1930s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - General, M-N, 1930s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - General, O-R, 1930s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - General, S-U, 1930s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - General, V-Z, 1960s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - General, First Names Only and Illegible, circa 1970s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - General Business Correspondence, 1930-1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - General Business Correspondence, 1946-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Greeting Cards, circa 1920s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3-9)
    Oversized material housed in Box 16, Folder 2
  - Helion, Jean, 1937-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Kandinsky, Wassily, 1930s-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Marcks, Gerhard and Maria, 1963-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Osver, Arthur, 1950-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13-16)
  - Prizes and Requisitions, 1940-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Purchases, 1956-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Richard York Gallery, 1987-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Schrag, Karl, 1940s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1969-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21-23)
  - Urban, Albert, 1946-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Y Labeled Correspondence (Y15-Y36), 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Oversized Greeting Cards from Box 2, Folder 4, Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Notes and Writings, 1922-2002; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 0.5 Linear feet Box 2
  Some of the material in this series is labeled with "G" and "Y" stickers as the green and yellow series.
  Series includes a biographical essay, a German diary, with translation, documenting Drewes' time in Europe from 1918-1920, a 1922 "love letter" to Drewes' first wife Margaret written in a bound notebook in verse form with a translation from the German, and notes on Drewes' trips to Europe from the 1960s-1980s.
  General notes on design and diagrams of class problems appear to have been written by Drewes' during his tenure at Washington University.
  Writings by others include two essays on Drewes.
  - By Drewes, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
    - Biographical Essay (G24), circa 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Diagrams of Class Problems, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Diary of Werner Drewes, English Translation, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Diary of Werner Drewes, 1918-1920, Translation of Manuscript to Modern German (G21-G23), 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 29-30)
    - "Farewell Love Letter to Margaret when she left for the Azores in 1922" (Y1A), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - "Farewell Love Letter to Margaret when she left for the Azores in 1922," Translation (Y1B), 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - General Notes on Design, circa 1950s-circa 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, Poems, circa 1950s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Notes on Drewes' Trips to Europe (G27), circa 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - By Others, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
    - Essay by Franz Geierhaas, English Translation (G25), "The Graphic Work of Werner Drewes", 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Essay on Drewes by Riedl (Y-40), 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Catalogs and Inventory Records, circa 1919-circa 1980s; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 2.3 Linear feet Boxes 2-6
  The bulk of the catalogs and index cards are labeled with blue stickers as the "B" series; two folders contain "T" series index cards. All material is arranged in alpha-numerical order according to these labels.
  Series contains inventory records of artwork maintained by Drewes throughout his career from the early 1900s-1980s. Catalogs document artwork by genre and may record any or all of the following: the date of execution, title and assigned number, a sketch of the artwork with descriptive notes such as subject and dimensions, and sales information where applicable. In some cases photos of artwork are affixed beside the sketch. A series of copies of some of the catalogs, compiled from the originals in the 1980s, is also included here.
  Index cards, which document artwork arranged by number, contain similar information but are accompanied in many cases by photographs, and negatives, of artwork rather than sketches.
  - Catalog B1: Oils, 1930s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Catalogs B2, B3: Oils, 1930s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Catalog B4: Oils, 1930s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Catalog B5A: Oils, 1930s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Catalog B5B: Oils, 1930s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Catalogs B6, B7: Watercolors, 1930s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs B8, B9: Prints, circa 1919-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Catalog B10: Prints, circa 1919-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Catalog B12: Prints, circa 1919-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Catalog B13: Collages, 1940s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Catalog B14, circa 1920s-circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Catalog B15: Prints, circa 1919-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Catalog, Not Numbered: Prints, circa 1919-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Catalog Notes for Wolfram Drewes, circa 1940s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Catalog Copies, B1, R2-R4, Y2-Y3, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
  - Catalog Copies B2, B3, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Catalog Copies B4, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
  - Catalog Copies B5A, B5B, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18-19)
  - Catalog Copies B6, B7, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Index Cards, Archival Resource Key (Box 4)
    - Cards for 1923-1944, B16, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Portrait Studies, 1924-1944, B16, circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Paintings, 1932-1944, B17, circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Paintings, 1932-1944, #191-337, B17, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Artwork, 1924-1950, #1-124, B18, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Artwork, 1924-1950, #125-241, B18, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Artwork, 1924-1950, #241-322, B18, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Artwork, 1924-1950, #322-400, B18, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Artwork, 1924-1950, #401-476, B18, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Artwork, 1924-1950, #477-526, B18, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Artwork, 1924-1950, #526-599, B18, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Artwork, 1951-1971, #600-655, B19, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Artwork, 1951-1971, #656-749, B19, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Artwork, 1951-1971, #750-800, B19, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Artwork, 1951-1971, #801-877, B19, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Artwork, 1951-1971, #878-933, B19, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Artwork, 1951-1971, #934-1016, B19, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Artwork, 1951-1971, #1017-1105, B19, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Artwork, 1951-1971, #1106-1199, B19, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Artwork, 1971-1985, #1200-1239, B20, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Artwork, 1971-19851, #1240-1298, B20, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Artwork, 1971-1985, #1299-1363, B20, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Artwork, 1971-1985, #1364-1428, B20, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Artwork, 1971-1985, #1429-1486, B20, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Artwork, 1971-1985, #1488-1535, B20, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Artwork, 1971-1985, #1536-1570, B20, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Artwork #T1-T109, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Artwork #T110-T159, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Price Lists and Miscellaneous Records, 1939, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Scrapbooks, 1920s-1985; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 3 Folders Box 5